ubuy.com 2009-06-20

# The place to buy anything and everything.

We believe that the establishment of trust and privacy is instrumental to the continued growth of the Internet. We have created this privacy statement to demonstrate our commitment to individual privacy. The policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our services. By using our web site, you agree to the terms and conditions set forth below. 

Collection of Personal Information 

We collect personal information including, without limitations, name, address, e-mail address, telephone, demographic data and member identification number from its members and users. We may collect such personal information as part of the registration process for members or when members or users submit comments or other correspondence to us through our web site or otherwise. Additionally, we may collect personal information through its web site by using cookies or other methods of monitoring web usage. We do not market, sell, or trade this information to any outside companies, but collected information may be shared with our business partners. We may, at times, use the demographic information as a marketing or promotional tool. When we do that, we will make sure it remains entirely anonymous. 

Cookies 

We use cookies to keep track of its members' and users' activity. The type of cookies we use do not get stored on your computer, rather they expire once the browser is closed. 

Security 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (a valid email address), unique identifiers (a password), financial information (credit card number), and demographic information (such as a zip code). When this type of information is collected it travels through the Internet in encrypted form. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), which provides strong cryptography, to transfer all of the personal information to us. Financial and login information (password) are encrypted and stored in that form on our servers.
